Guide to the Everett Education Association Records
Special Collections, University of Washington Libraries
- United Teachers of Everett records, circa 1971-1986; 1973-1986; 3849-002; 22.00 cubic feet
  - Secretaries and Teacher Aides Contract, Undated; Hand-written notes, memos, exploratory topics, bi-laws, memo from Seattle Teachers Association, Everett Secretaries contract, Everett Education Association and ETA Seattle Teachers Association bi-laws (Box 12, Folder 40)
  - Everett Education Association Contract, 1981; Hand-written contract surveys, contract analysis committee report, newsletters (Box 12, Folder 41)
  - Crisis Management Information, Undated; Booklets, surveys, newsletters, and flyers regarding what should happen in the event of different types of emergencies (Box 12, Folder 42)
  - Everett Education Association Election Information, 1974-1975; Flyers, memos, letters, notes and tallies for the Everett Education Association bi-laws and members (Box 12, Folder 43)
  - Everett Education Association Contract Court Cases, 1971; Legal documents, memos, and notes regarding improper teacher lay-offs / contract re-negotiations. Some rust damage and paper dis-coloration (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Liability Information, 1974; Inflation rates, school liability insurance policy, minority teacher information, front cover falling off insurance booklet (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - NEA Information, 1976-1977; NEA minimum affiliation standards and memo to local Presidents from Everett Education Association chapter heads (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - District Mail Use, 1979; Memos and copies of memos with hand-written notes addressing the use of district mail for Everett Education Association and affiliate organizations, with a collection of Pilchuck Uniserve newsletters (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Reading Continuum Discussions, 1975; Copy of transcript of discussion between Everett Education Association and Everett School District regarding the reading curriculum, with hand-written notes as well (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Reduction in Force Disagreement, 1974; copy of a letter explaining disagreement in Reduction in Force policy with corrections and response news (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Everett Vocational Counseling Information, 1976; Booklet outlining the importance and availability of vocational training for students (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Social Studies Teaching Methods, Undated; Booklet outlining methods of social studies teaching and the steps to teach students social studies in a small group setting, with questions and examples (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Curriculum Selection Policy, Undated; booklet with worksheets about how to change curriculum and how to evaluate current curriculum (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Budget Analysis Handbook, 1975; Booklet outlining how to budget, complete with worksheet copies (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Budget Analysis Documents, 1973-1976; Copies of budget notes, budget analysis handbooks, extra-large papers folded in half (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Monthly Enrolment Statistics, 1976-1977; Breakdown of students based on enrolment for the academic year by month and grade level (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - District Audit Information, 1976-1977; Copy of Washington State Audit of the Everett School District (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Washington Education Association Salary Information Part 1, 1978; Collection of memos, charts and worksheets, and flyers about Washington Teachers' salaries, in book form (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Washington Education Association Salary Information Part 2, 1978; Collection of memos, charts and worksheets, and flyers about Washington Teachers' salaries, in book form (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Everett School Board Minutes and Memos, 1949-1983; Copies of meeting minutes, memos, disciplinary actions considered, and hand-written notes (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Newspaper Clippings, 1980-1981; Advertisement purchasing information, newspaper clippings, some in separate parts, some extra-large / odd shaped and folded differently, Everett Education Association alerts in as well (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Correspondence with Other Organizations, 1981; Memos, letters, and invitations from other Everett organizations and labor / education organizations (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Education Guidelines, Undated; Memo on alternative education and laws on basic education availability (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Class Size Educational Materials, Undated; Cartoons, newspaper ads and radio spots to inform the community about problems regarding increased class sizes (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - Human Relations Commission Membership Guide, 1981; Booklet with Everett Education Association recruitment information, including dates, committee responsibilities, etc. (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - Legislative Information, 1981; Memos, newspaper articles, legislative hand-book, hand-written annotations, tables and graphs itemizing funding allocations (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - Media Campaign, Undated; Hand-written plan on how to emphasize large class sizes as an educational problem (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - Labor Council Letters, 1981; Letters and flyers sent out by the AFL/CIO to the Everett Education Association (Box 13, Folder 24)
  - Staff Changes and Everett Education Association Membership, 1981; Letters, memos, booklets about membership in the Everett Education Association and as teachers in the Everett School District (Box 13, Folder 25)
  - National Education Association Materials, 1981; Cartoons, memos, allocation of delegates booklet, and other flyers from the National Education Association (Box 13, Folder 26)
  - Office Rental Information, 1981; Copies of hand-written and typed documents regarding room rental agreements and break-downs (Box 13, Folder 27)
  - Bargaining Survey Information, 1983; Surveys sent out to teachers with hand-written comments, some torn corners and rust damage (Box 13, Folder 28)
  - Pilchuck Uniserv Letters, 1981-1982; Letters and Information from Pilchuck Uniserv council, some rust damage and bended corners of paper (Box 13, Folder 29)
  - Alternative Education, 1980; Outline and information regarding the Everett Education Association's Public Schools for Alternative Education committee (Box 13, Folder 30)
  - Retired Teacher's Association, 1980; carbon copy of hand-written letter, booklet of Retired Teachers Association members, copy of newspaper clipping with information and comments (Box 13, Folder 31)
  - Everett School Board Agendas, 1980-1981; Monthly agendas from the Everett School District, incomplete and out of chronological order (Box 13, Folder 32)
  - Leave Requests, 1981; Leave Requests for Mike Sells in 1981 (Box 13, Folder 33)
  - Extra-Curricular Salaries, 1983-1984; Extra-curricular stipend charts, comparative among districts and surveys (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Sick Leave, 1980; Information for sick leave and how teachers can apply for sick leave (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Washington Education Association, 1980-1981; Newsletters and memos from the WEA to the local chapters regarding budget information and holidays (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Election Rules and Bi-Laws, 1980; Everett Education Association election information, multiple copies of most parts of the document (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Reduction in Force Information, 1981; List and contact info for teachers laid off with legal documentation and information to assist them (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Rally '82 Information, 1982; Organizational documents and letters for get out the vote in the 1982 election with sample letters and budgets (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - WEA Dues Contract, 1982 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Everett Education Association Ballots, 1982; Nominations and ballots for Everett Education Association officers and Labor Caucus members (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Phone Assessments, Undated; Hand-written instructions of surveys and copies of phone surveys (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Class Size Reports, Undated; Hand-written notes about elementary class sizes and graphs of district wide class sizes and teacher ratios (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Miscellaneous Organizational Documents, 1980-1981; Meeting notes, agendas, insurance information, membership information, etc. (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Everett Central Business District Study, 1983; Booklet outlining study / survey of the central business district in Everett and the effects on different sectors (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Everett Development Strategy, 1983; Economic assessment and plan of action for the Everett professional / business sector (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - American Federation of Teachers Liability Insurance, Undated; Information about teacher liability and reasons why they should have liability insurance, also data on how teachers can sign up for it (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - American Federation of Teachers Publications, 1984; Flyers and newsletters produced by the American Federation of Teachers regarding organizational history, teaching tips, and activities (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Action Committee Staff Assessment, 1983; Copy of results page, original surveys given to teachers and supporting data (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Asbestos Timeline, 1984; Detailed legal document regarding asbestos recognition and removal (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - American Education Week, 1985; Flyers, hand-outs, poster, proclamation forms, etc. to inform members of the community about American Education Week and how they can get involved (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Everett Education Association Leave Report, 1984; Name, reason, and days Everett Education Association members had off (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - Superintendent Salaries, 1981-1982; Newspaper article copy, memos, and graph of superintendent salaries in Washington State, and how some are higher than others (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - Business Week Information, 1984; copy of hand-written outline and half-sheet memo (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - Central Washington School Employees Benefit Trust, 1985; booklet, memos, and agreements regarding the Central Washington Benefit Trust (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - Citizens for Everett Public Schools Association, 1985; Founding documents and bi-laws for the Citizens for Everett Public Schools Association (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - Committee Appointments, 1984; parts of paper and hand-written notes of people and what committees they might be interested in being on (Box 14, Folder 23)
  - Deferred Salary Leave Plan, Undated; Standard salary leave plan with fill in the blanks to be filled in by other people (Box 14, Folder 24)
  - Democratic Caucus Summary, 1985; Washington State Senate summary of legislative actions taken, goals and results, etc. (Box 14, Folder 25)
  - Snohomish County Democrats, Undated; copy of membership records, and outline of bi-laws (Box 14, Folder 26)
  - Everett Education Association Goals for 1984, List of goals, some with notes, for the Everett Education Association (Box 14, Folder 27)
  - Uniserve Grant Request, 1983; Instructions, budget information, and hand-written information regarding grant request to the Uniserve Council from the Everett Education Association (Box 14, Folder 28)
  - Everett Community Profile, 1983 (Box 14, Folder 29)
  - Internal Assessment Survey, 1983 (Box 14, Folder 30)
  - Teacher Workday/Mini-Survey, 1985 (Box 14, Folder 31)
  - 1982-1983 Telephone Tree, Phone numbers (Box 14, Folder 32)
  - Extended Day Monitoring Form, 1985 (Box 14, Folder 33)
  - State General Report & District Level Summaries- 1984 Washington Statewide Educational Assessment 4th Grade (Box 14, Folder 34)
  - State General Report & District Level Summaries- 1983 Washington Statewide Educational Assessment 4th Grade (Box 14, Folder 35)
  - 1985 Washington Education Association Representative Handbook (Box 14, Folder 36)
  - Washington Education Association & National Education Association Conventions Nomination Data, 1982 (Box 14, Folder 37)
  - The Paramount Duty- Report of the WA State Temporary Committee on Educational Policies, Structure and Management, 1985 (Box 14, Folder 38)
  - Everett Education Association/United Teachers of Everett Address List- Blank, Undated (Box 14, Folder 39)
  - Survey on Supplemental Contract Payment, 1984 (Box 14, Folder 40)
  - 1983 Levy/Bond Survey (Box 14, Folder 41)
  - Surveys on Activities/Insurance Data, 1983; Some pages stuck together (Box 14, Folder 42)
  - Bargaining Surveys, 1983 (Box 14, Folder 43)
  - Substitute Policy/Issues Survey 1982 (Box 14, Folder 44)
  - Hourly Rates of Pay/Extracurricular Issue Survey 1982 (Box 14, Folder 45)
  - Educational Credits/Work Day/Compensation Issue Survey 1982 (Box 14, Folder 46)
  - Personal Tax Survival- Investment Seminar Program, 1985 (Box 14, Folder 47)
  - Letters re: Lawsuit Withdrawal 1982 (Box 14, Folder 48)
  - Profiles of Excellence- Program and Responses, 1981 (Box 14, Folder 49)
  - 1984 Presidential Election Handbook (Box 14, Folder 50)
  - 1980 Election Financing Fact Book (Box 14, Folder 51)
  - National Women's History Week Curriculum 1983 (Box 14, Folder 52)
  - Documents on the Merit Pay Debate, 1983 (Box 14, Folder 53)
  - Memo of Agreement Kinard/Pringle ('82-'83), 1983 (Box 14, Folder 54)
  - Limiting Executive Board Terms Survey, 1985 (Box 14, Folder 55)
  - Legislative Notes 1982 (Box 14, Folder 56)
  - 1985 Legislation, 1984 (Box 14, Folder 57)
  - Information from Other Districts, 1982-1983 (Box 14, Folder 58)
  - The Importance of Recognition and Enrichment Programs for America's Teachers, 1984 (Box 14, Folder 59)
  - Subjective vs. Objective Reality: The Effect of Human Relations Training Exercises on a High School Class as Viewed by an Idealistic/Disenchanted Teacher, 1981 (Box 14, Folder 60)
  - Wayne Hamilton National Education Association Membership, Undated (Box 14, Folder 61)
  - Suggestions for Financial Planning Seminar, Undated (Box 14, Folder 62)
  - 1984 4th Grade Test Results (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Fort Worden Wellness Team Wellness Day, 1985 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Employment & Training You Subcommittee Orientation Manual, 1982 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Information for Dislocated Workers- Employment Security Department (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Everett No. 2 Budget for Fiscal Year 1982-1983 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Everett No. 2 Budget for Fiscal Year 1983-1984 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Everett School District #2 Employee Benefits Program, 1982 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - 1982-1987 District-wide Plan for Vocational Education Everett School District #2 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Lay Off and Recall Placement Within Categories 1983-1984 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Everett Education Association Election Materials- Voter Pamphlet (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Labor Caucus Official Ballots, 1984 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Negotiations- Bargaining Alert/ MLK Birthday, 1984 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Professional Air Traffic Controllers Organization (PATCO) Strike, 1981 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Urban Family's Budget, 1982 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - The Union Line News- TOPCO products, 1984 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Data Sheets for Everett Education Association members in Court Case, 1981 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - F1 and F1A Forms- Everett School Board Members (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence and Financial Information from WA. Superintendent of Public Instruction 1983 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Everett Housing Authority- Documents, 1982-1984 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Minutes, Correspondence, Budget, misc. Documents of the Everett Housing Authority, 1982 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Budgets, Correspondence and "Journal of Housing", 1982 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - West Coast Industrial Relations Association, Lumber Production and Industrial Workers of America Strike, Manual for Preventing Formation of Unions, other various WCIRA Involvements, 1983 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Educational Staff Associate Commission, Undated (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Problems with Experience Credits, 1985 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Karen Hansen Memo, c. 1988 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Report on "Creating our Future in Education", 1985 (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Election Data for Delegate to WA AFL-CIO Endorsing Convention, 1987-1988 (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - Notes for Meeting with Senator Bailey, 1987 (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - Speech to 30th District Democrats re: Housing, 1987 (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - University Credits and Letter re: Voter Registrar, 1986 (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - Bargaining Correspondence, Information, etc. 1985-1986 (Box 16, Folder 21)
  - Chiropractic Services Bureau Benefits, 1984 (Box 16, Folder 22)
  - Educational Clinics and Redistricting Case, 1982-1984 (Box 16, Folder 23)
  - Everett Parents and Teachers Association Council Directory, 1985-1986 (Box 16, Folder 24)
  - Evergreen Middle School Advisory Program Survey, Undated (Box 16, Folder 25)
  - Evergreen Organizing Activities 1985-1986 (Box 16, Folder 26)
  - Focus on Public Education, 1983 (Box 16, Folder 27)
  - Florida Teacher Performance Manual, 1987 (Box 16, Folder 28)
  - Letter re: IMPACT Program, 1985 (Box 16, Folder 29)
  - "Writing it Off"- How to Deduct a Personal Computer on your Tax Return, 1984 (Box 16, Folder 30)
  - Summary of Kindergarten Conference Questionnaire, 1988 (Box 16, Folder 31)
  - Information re: Lowell- Joy Lansdowne, Undated (Box 16, Folder 32)
  - Michael Wartelle Leave Request, 1986-1987 (Box 16, Folder 33)
  - Legislative Information- 99th Congress, 1985-1986 (Box 16, Folder 34)
  - Late Start Days Survey, 1986 (Box 16, Folder 35)
  - Washington Education Association/ Minority Leadership Training Program, 1986 (Box 16, Folder 36)
  - Monroe Elementary Carpet Problem, 1987 (Box 16, Folder 37)
  - "More Effective Schools"- Ray Russman, 1986 (Box 16, Folder 38)
  - National Education Association Budgets 1983-1984, 1984-1985, 1985-1986, 1983-1986 (Box 16, Folder 39)
  - National Education Association 1986 Annual Meeting (Box 16, Folder 40)
  - 1986-1987 Nomination forms for Election (Box 16, Folder 41)
  - Bankruptcy of NORD Co., 1986 (Box 16, Folder 42)
  - Salary Increase Determination Data, 1985 (Box 16, Folder 43)
  - Member/Non-Member Contact Lists, 1985 (Box 16, Folder 44)
  - Everett Education Association Membership Contact Cards, Undated (Box 16, Folder 45)
  - Everett Education Association/United Teachers of Everett Goals/Activities/Calendar, 1985-1986 (Box 16, Folder 46)
  - Networks, 1985-1986 (Box 16, Folder 47)
  - Nomination Forms for VP/Director-at-Large, 1985-1986 (Box 16, Folder 48)
  - Everett Education Association/United Teachers of Everett President's Log 1986 (Box 16, Folder 49)
  - Levy Fundraising, 1985 (Box 16, Folder 50)
  - Late Start Surveys, 1987 (Box 16, Folder 51)
  - Correspondence Everett Education Association Policies re: Merger, 1973 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Merger Background Information, 1973-1974 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - 1974 National Education Association Convention/ Merger Materials and Precedents (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Summer 1973 Preliminary Discussion of Merger (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Everett Education Association/Everett Federation of Teachers Membership Campaigns, 1980 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Everett Education Association Budget Reports 1980 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Everett Education Association Budget Reports 1977-1982 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Everett Education Association Newsletters, 1968-1970 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - "NEA Now" Newsletters, 1980-1981 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Washington Education Association Legislative Outlook, 1981 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Everett School District #2 Bulletin, 1981 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Retirement Seminar, 1974; PHOTOS (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - National Education Association President, 1971-1971; PHOTO (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Executive Board, 1971-1972; PHOTOS (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - Office, 1971-1972; PHOTOS (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - General Meeting, Sept. 1971; PHOTOS (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - Legislative Rally, Spring 1971; PHOTOS (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - Salmon Barbecue, 1971; PHOTOS (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - Representative Assembly, Oct 1971; PHOTOS (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - Teacher Spotlight - Dobson, 1971; PHOTOS (Box 17, Folder 20)
  - Editor, 1971-1972; PHOTOS (Box 17, Folder 21)
  - Salmon BBQ & Open House, Sept 1973; PHOTOS (Box 17, Folder 22)
  - Misc. Everett Education Association Pictures- 1974, PHOTOS (Box 17, Folder 23)
  - BR Workshop, 1973; PHOTOS (Box 17, Folder 24)
  - Membership Lists and Campaign, Undated (Box 17, Folder 25)
  - Membership Information- PULSE membership, Contact Information, Copies of Washington Education Association/National Education Association Membership Cards, 1979-1981 (Box 17, Folder 26)
  - Everett Education Association Bylaws, Election Timeline and Election Results, 1980 (Box 17, Folder 27)
  - Everett Chamber of Commerce Directory and Community Action Committee Agendas, 1981 (Box 17, Folder 28)
  - Community Action Committee Budget and Finances, 1981-1982 (Box 17, Folder 29)
  - Correspondence Re: Community Newsletter and "The Educator", 1980-1982 (Box 17, Folder 30)
  - Newsletter Year End Report, 1980 (Box 17, Folder 31)
  - Everett Education Association- "The Educator" Community Newsletter, 1980-1982 (Box 17, Folder 32)
  - Discipline Workshop Planning, 1981 (Box 17, Folder 33)
  - Survey on Discipline and Analysis, 1981 (Box 17, Folder 34)
  - Discipline Forum Committee Evaluation, 1981 (Box 17, Folder 35)
  - Flier for Student Discipline Forum, 1981 (Box 17, Folder 36)
  - Community Action Discipline Agenda Forum Planning Meeting, 1981 (Box 17, Folder 37)
  - Radio Advertising Discipline Forum, 1981 (Box 17, Folder 38)
  - Newspaper Advertising and Photographs for Discipline Forum, 1981; PHOTOS (Box 17, Folder 39)
  - Planning for Discipline Workshop/ Seattle Teacher's Association "Communicator", 1980-1981 (Box 17, Folder 40)
  - Discipline Forum Materials, 1980-1981 (Box 17, Folder 41)
  - Posters/Pamphlets for Discipline Forum, 1981 (Box 17, Folder 42)
  - Slide Presentation for Discipline Forum, 1981 (Box 17, Folder 43)
  - Legal opinion- Contracts etc.- W. Mitchell Cogdill, 1971 (Box 17, Folder 44)
  - Legal Opinion- Substitute Contracts, 1973 (Box 17, Folder 45)
  - Legal Opinion - School Board Proposed Evaluation Procedure/Criteria and Grievances, 1973 (Box 17, Folder 46)
  - Legal Advice- Nondiscrimination in Policies, etc., 1974 (Box 17, Folder 47)
  - Legal Advice- 1st Draft of 1971-1972 Proposed Master Contract (Box 17, Folder 48)
  - Legal Opinion: Minority Plank of Board's Proposed Reduction in Force Policy, 1974 (Box 17, Folder 49)
  - Reduction in Force in Light of Williams v. Board of Directors of Endicott School District Appeal Court Decision, 1974 (Box 17, Folder 50)
  - Reduction in Force as it Concerns Seniority, 1974 (Box 17, Folder 51)
  - Legal Opinion- Agency Shop 1973 (Box 17, Folder 52)
  - Legal Opinion- Hold Harmless Absence Due to Injury, 1973 (Box 17, Folder 53)
  - Everett Education Association v. Everett School District No. 2- Substitutes, 1974 (Box 17, Folder 54)
  - Opinion in Truax vs. Edmonds School District No. 15 of Snohomish Co. WA, 1971 (Box 17, Folder 55)
  - Janice Broz v. Board of Directors of Everett School District No.2/ Maternity Cases, 1975-1976 (Box 17, Folder 56)
  - Maternity Leave, 1973 (Box 17, Folder 57)
  - Strike Related Court Case- Warren Hewitt, 1977 (Box 17, Folder 58)
  - Strike Related Court Case- Harold McNeil, 1977 (Box 17, Folder 59)
  - Strike Related Court Case- Gordon Mikkikan, 1976 (Box 17, Folder 60)
  - Substitute Grievance Court Case, 1975 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Court Case- Salary Issue Materials, 1974 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Everett Education Association v. Everett School District- Salary Issue Negotiation, 1974 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Delora J. Abbey v. Everett School District No. 2: Non Renewal Legal Forms, 1972 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Settlement/Oral Examination Walthall v. Everett School District and Everett Education Association vs. Everett School District, 1976-1977 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Wennberg v. Everett School District No. 1980 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Non-Renewal Lawsuit, 1981 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Unemployment Compensation Appeal Case, 1980-1983 (Box 18, Folder 8)